titlepro247.com 2019-06-05

# BlackKnightInc.com Privacy Notice

At Black Knight, Inc., we respect and believe it is important to protect the privacy of consumers and our customers. This Privacy Notice explains how we collect, use, and protect any information that we collect from you, when and to whom we disclose such information, and the choices you have about the use of that information. A summary of the Privacy Notice is below, and we encourage you to review the entirety of the Privacy Notice following this summary. As a consumer, you can opt-out of certain disclosures by following our opt-out procedure set forth at the end of this Privacy Notice.

**​Personal Information Collected as a Third Party Service Provider.** When we collect as a third party service provider, we do so solely to provide services to lending institutions and mortgage loan servicers. The privacy notices of those lending institutions or mortgage loan servicers shall apply and you should refer to those privacy notices and/or contact them to understand how your Personal Information will be used. | ​ **Types of Information Collected**. You may provide us with certain personal information about you, like your contact information, account information, demographic information, social security number (SSN), driver’s license, passport, other government ID numbers, and/or financial information. We may also receive browsing information from your Internet browser, computer, and/or mobile device.  
---|---  
​ **How Information is Collected**. We may collect personal information from you via applications, forms, and correspondence we receive from you and others related to transactions with you. When you visit our websites, we automatically collect and store certain information available to us through your Internet browser or computer equipment. | ​ **Use of Collected Information**. We request and use your personal information to provide products and services to you, to improve our products and services, and to communicate with you about these products and services. We may also share your contact information with our affiliates for marketing purposes unless prohibited by applicable law or otherwise stated herein.  
​ **When Information is Disclosed**. We may disclose your information to our affiliates and/or nonaffiliated parties providing services for you or us, to law enforcement agencies or governmental authorities, and as required by law. | ​ **Choices With Your Information**. Your decision to submit information to us is entirely up to you. You can opt-out of certain disclosure or use of your information or choose to not provide any personal information to us.  
**​ Password and Security**. We may require the use of encryption technologies provided for your protection. We use reasonable precautions to protect the privacy of your username, password, and user account information, but we cannot guarantee the security of all information transferred over the Internet. | **Information From Children**. We do not knowingly collect information from children who are under the age of 13, and our website and other services are not intended to attract children.  
**​Privacy Outside the Website.** We are not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties, even if our website links to those parties’ websites. | ​ **Access and Correction**. In the event this is applicable to you, if you desire to access or correct your personal information held by Black Knight, please contact us in the manner specified at the end of this Privacy Notice. If we receive your personal information in our capacity as a third party service provider, see the section titled _The California Online Privacy Protection Act_.  
**The California Online Privacy Protection Act.** Some Black Knight companies provide services to lending institutions and mortgage loan servicers and, in some cases, their websites collect information. Those parties are responsible for taking action or making changes to any consumer information submitted through those websites. | **European Users**. The website and our products and services are hosted in the United States and are governed by United States law. If you are using the website or our products or services from outside the United States, your Personal Information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States. The data protection and privacy laws of the United States might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using the website or our products and services, you consent to your Personal Information being transferred to our facilities and to the facilities of those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Notice.  
**Employment Opportunities.** We may allow prospective employees to request additional job opportunity information online. By submitting your information, you consent to its dissemination to, and use by, us and our affiliates. | **Not Financial Advice.** We are not providing financial opinions or advice on any of the matters discussed or included on the website, and we will not be liable to any party for any act or failure to act relating to any advice listed on the website.  
**Your Consent To This Privacy Notice.** By submitting information to us or by using our website, you are accepting and agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Notice. | ** **  
  
Black Knight, Inc. (NYSE: BKI) (“Black Knight”, “our,” “us” or “we”) is a leading provider of integrated technology, data, and analytics solutions that facilitate and automate many of the business processes across the mortgage lifecycle. Black Knight is committed to being a premier business partner that lending institutions and mortgage loan servicers (collectively, “Lenders and Servicers”) rely on to achieve their strategic goals, realize greater success and better serve their customers by delivering best-in-class technology, services and insight with a relentless commitment to excellence, innovation, integrity, and leadership.

Black Knight respects and is committed to protecting your privacy. We will take reasonable steps to provide that your Personal Information (as defined herein) and Browsing Information (as defined herein) will only be used in compliance with this Privacy Notice and applicable privacy-related laws. This Privacy Notice is only in effect for Personal Information and Browsing Information collected and/or owned by or on behalf of Black Knight through any Black Knight website, online service, or application of Black Knight (collectively, the “Website”). This Privacy Notice is in effect no matter the method of collection ( _e.g._ , mail, facsimile, sign-up/sign-in page, survey, promotion), including, without limitation, collection through our Website.

**Personal Information Collected as a Third Party Service Provider**

In almost all cases that Black Knight is receiving Personal Information, it is acting as a third party service provider to a Lender or Servicer. In such cases, we may collect or receive Personal Information about or from individuals for the sole purpose of providing services to or on behalf of such Lenders or Servicers. In cases where Black Knight is providing services to or on behalf of such Lenders or Servicers, we do not share consumer information with third parties, other than (1) those with which the Lender or Servicer has contracted to interface with the Black Knight consumer application, (2) law enforcement or other governmental authority in connection with an investigation, or civil or criminal subpoenas or court orders, or (3) as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Notice. The privacy notices of those Lenders and Servicers shall apply and you should refer to those privacy notices and/or contact your Lender or Servicer to understand how your Personal Information will be used by such Lenders or Servicers. We are not responsible or liable for the content, privacy policies, or practices of third parties.

**Types of Information Collected**

We, and any third party we engage for the purpose of administering, operating, hosting, configuring, designing, maintaining and providing internal support for our Website, may collect two types of information from you: Personal Information and Browsing Information.

Personal Information. Black Knight may collect the following categories of personal information (“Personal Information”), which may include, among other things:

  * contact information ( _e.g._ , first and last name, mailing or property address, phone number, email address);
  * user name, password, and security questions and answers;
  * demographic information ( _e.g._ , date of birth, gender, marital status);
  * social security number (SSN), driver’s license, passport, and other government ID numbers;
  * loan account information ( _e.g._ , loan number);
  * bank account and credit/debit card numbers; and
  * other personal information needed from you to provide real estate-related and loan-related services to you.

Browsing Information. Black Knight may collect the following categories of browsing information (“Browsing Information”), which may include, among other things:

  * Internet Protocol (or IP) address or device ID/UDID, protocol and sequence information;
  * browser language and type;
  * domain name system requests;
  * browsing history, such as time spent at a domain, time and date of your visit, and number of clicks;
  * http headers, application client and server banners;
  * operating system and fingerprinting data; and
  * aggregated information, including De-identified Data (as defined herein).

**How Information is Collected**

In the course of our business, we may collect Personal Information about you from the following sources:

  * applications or other forms we receive from you or your authorized representative, which may include information about your assets and income and identifying information, such as name, address and SSN;
  * the correspondence you and others send to us;
  * information we receive from you through the Website;
  * information about your transactions with, or services performed by, us, our affiliates or nonaffiliated third parties;
  * information we receive from your computer or mobile device;
  * information we receive from our partners or service providers;
  * information from consumer or other reporting agencies and public records maintained by governmental entities that we obtain directly from those entities, from our affiliates or others, such as your creditworthiness and credit history; and
  * information we receive from other sources, as permitted by applicable laws, rules, and regulations.

If you visit or use our Website, we may collect Browsing Information from you as follows:

  * _Browser Log Files_. Our servers automatically log each visitor to the Website and collect and record certain browsing information about each visitor. The Browsing Information includes only generic information and reveals nothing personal about the user.
  * _Cookies_. When you visit our Website, a “cookie” may be sent to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. When you visit the Website again, the cookie allows the Website to recognize your computer. Cookies may store user preferences and other information. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing your Internet browser settings, which may impair or limit some functionality of the Website.
  * _Web Beacons_. Some of our web pages and electronic communications may contain images, which may or may not be visible to you, known as Web Beacons (sometimes referred to as ‘clear gifs’). Web Beacons collect only limited information that includes a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web Beacon resides. We may also carry Web Beacons placed by third party advertisers.
  * _Unique Identifier_. We may assign you a unique internal identifier to help keep track of your future visits. We use this information to gather aggregate demographic information about our visitors, and we may use it to personalize the information you see on the Website and some of the electronic communications you receive from us. We keep this information for our internal use.

**Use of Collected Information**

Information collected by Black Knight is used for the following, primary purposes:

  * To provide products and services to you or any affiliate or third party who is obtaining services on your behalf or in connection with a transaction involving you.
  * To improve our products and services.
  * To personalize your experience of the Website.
  * To communicate with you and to inform you about Black Knight, our Black Knight affiliates’ and third parties’ products and services, jointly or independently.

**When Information Is Disclosed**

We may provide your Personal Information (excluding information we receive from consumer or other credit reporting agencies) and Browsing Information to various individuals and companies, as permitted by law, without obtaining your prior authorization. Such laws do not allow consumers to restrict these disclosures. Please see the section below titled _Choices with Your Personal Information_ to learn how to limit the discretionary disclosure of your Personal Information and Browsing Information.

Disclosures of your Personal Information may be made to the following categories of affiliates and nonaffiliated third parties, unless prohibited by applicable law:

  * to third parties to provide you with services you have requested, and to enable us to detect or prevent criminal activity, fraud, material misrepresentation, or nondisclosure;
  * to our affiliate financial service providers for their use to market their products or services to you;
  * to nonaffiliated third party service providers who provide or perform services on our behalf and use the disclosed information only in connection with such services;
  * to nonaffiliated third party service providers with whom we perform joint marketing, pursuant to an agreement with them to market financial products or services to you;
  * to law enforcement or other governmental authority in connection with an investigation, or civil or criminal subpoena or court order;
  * to lenders, lien holders, judgment creditors, or other parties claiming an interest in title whose claim or interest must be determined, settled, paid, or released prior to closing; and
  * other third parties for whom you have given us written authorization to disclose your Personal Information.

We may disclose Personal Information and/or Browsing Information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to:

  * comply with a legal process or applicable laws;
  * enforce this Privacy Notice;
  * take precautions against liability and investigate or respond to claims that any material, document, image, graphic, logo, design, audio, video or any other information provided by you violates the rights of a third party;
  * protect the rights, property or personal safety of Black Knight, its users or the public, which includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction, and, if required by law, disclosing information to U.S. federal and state governmental agencies; or
  * to investigate potential unauthorized access or misuse of our Website.

We maintain reasonable safeguards to keep your Personal Information secure. When we provide Personal Information to our affiliates or third party service providers as discussed in this Privacy Notice, we require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Notice or in a manner that complies with applicable privacy laws. The use of your information by a trusted business partner may be subject to that party’s own Privacy Notice. Unless permitted by law, we do not disclose information we collect from consumer or credit reporting agencies with our affiliates or others without your consent.

In addition to the other rights herein, we have the right to share and use, for any purpose, the collected Personal Information that is in an aggregated, anonymized form, such that you are not identified (collectively, “De-identified Data”).

We reserve the right to transfer your Personal Information, Browsing Information, and any other information, in connection with the sale or other disposition of all or part of the Black Knight business and/or assets, or in the event of our bankruptcy, reorganization, insolvency, receivership or an assignment for the benefit of creditors. You expressly agree and consent to the use and/or transfer of the foregoing information in connection with any of the above described proceedings. We cannot and will not be responsible for any breach of security by any third party or for any actions of any third party that receives any of the information that is disclosed to us.

We may disclose your Personal Information for any purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information. We may also disclose your Personal Information with your permission or as directed by you.

**Choices with Your Information**

Whether you submit Personal Information or Browsing Information to Black Knight is entirely up to you. If you decide not to submit Personal Information or Browsing Information, Black Knight may not be able to provide certain services or products to you. The uses of your Personal Information and/or Browsing Information that, by law, you cannot limit, include:

  * for our everyday business purposes – to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), to respond to law enforcement or other governmental authority in connection with an investigation, or civil or criminal subpoenas or court orders, or report to credit bureaus;
  * for our own marketing purposes;
  * for joint marketing with financial companies; and
  * for our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your transactions and experiences.

You may choose to prevent Black Knight from disclosing or using your Personal Information and/or Browsing Information under the following circumstances (“opt-out”):

  * for our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness; and
  * for our affiliates to market to you.

To the extent permitted above, you may opt-out of disclosure or use of your Personal Information and Browsing Information by notifying us by one of the methods at the end of this Privacy Notice. We do not share your Personal Information with non-affiliates for their direct marketing purposes.

Please note that opting out of the disclosure and use of your Personal Information as a prospective employee may prevent you from being hired as an employee to the extent you are using the Website to apply for an open position.

_For California and Delaware Residents_ : We will not share your Personal Information and Browsing Information with nonaffiliated third parties, except as permitted by law. Currently, we do not recognize “do not track” requests from Internet browsers and similar devices.

_For California Residents_ : Under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents who provide certain personally identifiable information in connection with obtaining products or services for personal, family, or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us (once a calendar year) information about the customer information we shared (if any) with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately prior calendar year ( _e.g._ , requests made in 2018 will receive information regarding 2017 sharing activities, if any). To obtain this information, please send an email message to [privacy@bkfs.com](mailto:privacy@bkfs.com) with “Request for California Privacy Information” in the subject line and in the body of your message. We will provide the requested information to you at your email address in response. Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the “Shine the Light” requirements, and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.

Under California Civil Code Section 1789.3, California users are entitled to the following consumer rights notice: If you have a question or complaint regarding the services or products provided through the Website, please send an email to [privacy@bkfs.com](mailto:privacy@bkfs.com). You may also contact us by writing to 601 Riverside Avenue, Jacksonville, Florida 32204, or by calling us at 904.854.5100 or 833.256.4448 (Toll-free). California residents may reach the Complaint Assistance Unit of the Division of Consumer Services of the California Department of Consumer Affairs by mail at 1625 North Market Blvd., Suite N 112, Sacramento, CA 95834, or by telephone at (916) 445-1254 or (800) 952-5210.

_For Nevada Residents_ : You may be placed on our internal Do Not Call List by calling (833.256.4448) or by contacting us via the information set forth at the end of this Privacy Notice. Nevada law requires that we also provide you with the following contact information: Bureau of Consumer Protection, Office of the Nevada Attorney General, 555 E. Washington St., Suite 3900, Las Vegas, NV 89101; Phone number: 702.486.3132; email: [BCPINFO@ag.state.nv.us.](mailto:BCPINFO@ag.state.nv.us)

_For Oregon Residents_ : We will not share your Personal Information and Browsing Information with nonaffiliated third parties for marketing purposes, except after you have been informed by us of such sharing and had an opportunity to indicate that you do not want a disclosure made for marketing purposes.

_For Vermont Residents_ : We will not share your Personal Information and Browsing Information with nonaffiliated third parties, except as permitted by Vermont law, such as to process your transactions or to maintain your account. In addition, we will not share information about your creditworthiness with our affiliates except with your authorization. For joint marketing in Vermont, we will only disclose your name, contact information and information about your transactions.

**Passwords and Security**

For certain features or services available through the Website, we may require the use of encryption technologies provided for your protection. Certain users of the Website may be able to create a user account to access certain features of our Website. We use reasonable precautions to protect the privacy of your username, password, and other user account information.

You are ultimately responsible for protecting your username, password, and other user account information from disclosure to third parties, and you are not permitted to circumvent the use of required encryption technologies. You agree to: (a) immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your username, password, and/or user account information, and/or any other breach of security; and (b) make sure that you log out from your user account at the end of each session. While we may provide certain encryption technologies and use other reasonable precautions to protect your confidential information and provide suitable security, we do not and cannot guarantee or warrant that any information transmitted through the Internet is secure, or that such transmissions are free from delay, interruption, interception or error.

**Information from Children**

The Website is meant for adults. We do not collect Personal Information from any person that we know to be under the age of thirteen (13) without permission from a parent or legal guardian. Specifically, the Website is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of thirteen (13). You affirm that you are over the age of 13 and will abide by the terms of this Privacy Notice.

Parents and legal guardians should be aware that this Privacy Notice will govern our use of Personal Information, but also that information that is voluntarily given by children – or others – in email exchanges, bulletin boards, or the like, may be used by other parties to generate unsolicited communications. We encourage all parents and legal guardians to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet.

**Privacy Outside the Website**

The Website may contain links to other websites. Black Knight is not and cannot be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any of those other websites. Please check with those websites in order to determine their privacy policies and your rights under them.

We may use the services of third party service providers, for example to process payments and other transactions. By using our Website, you grant us all necessary rights and consents under applicable laws to disclose to our third party service providers – or allow such third party service providers to collect, use, retain, and disclose – any Personal Information for purposes of providing services to you, including data that we may collect directly from you using cookies or other similar means.

**Access and Correction**

To update or correct your Personal Information in the possession of Black Knight, please contact us in the manner specified at the end of this Privacy Notice. However, in those cases where we are acting as a third party service provider to a Lender or Servicer, you must contact your Lender or Servicer. (See the section below titled _The California Online Privacy Protection Act_ below for additional information.)

**The California Online Privacy Protection Act**

As noted above, for some Black Knight Websites we may be acting as a third party service provider to a Lender or Servicer. In those instances, we may collect certain information on behalf of that Lender or Servicer. During these transactions, we may collect some or all of the information on behalf of the Lender or Servicer that is described in the section above titled _Types of Information Collected_.

The information you submit is then transferred to your Lender or Servicer by way of our services. The Lender or Servicer is responsible for taking action or making changes to any consumer information that is submitted through the Website. For example, if you believe that your payment or user information is incorrect, you must contact your Lender or Servicer.

Generally, we retain the information that you submit to us for 90 days. In some instances, we may retain the information for up to 270 days. After 90 days (or 270 days, as applicable), we destroy all of the customer data and information that was submitted to us. If we receive a timely request from you, we can provide the information to the applicable Lender or Servicer that is acting on your behalf before we purge our workspace of such information.

If you are receiving consumer services and have questions regarding the choices you have with regard to your personal information or how to access or correct your personal information, you should contact your Lender or Servicer.

**European Union Users**

The Website and our products and services are hosted in the United States and are governed by United States law. If you are using the Website or our products or services from outside the United States, please be aware that your Personal Information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using the Website or our products and services, you consent to your Personal Information being transferred to our facilities and to the facilities of those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Notice.

**Employment Opportunities**

For individuals interested in job opportunities with us, the Website may allow prospective employees to request additional job opportunity information and apply for a job online. We, or our third party service providers, may use the Website to collect Personal Information from prospective employees for human resources recruitment purposes. Such Personal Information may include your resume information, employment history, and information related to your race or disabilities. By submitting any of the foregoing information, you consent to its dissemination to, and use by, us and our affiliates. The foregoing also applies to job application inquiries and submissions that you may transmit to us other than through the Website.

**Not Financial Advice**

You acknowledge and agree that by providing you with access to and use of the Website, we are not providing financial opinions or advice on any of the matters discussed or included on the Website, and we will not be liable to any party for any act or failure to act relating to any advice listed on the Website. You further acknowledge that none of the information contained on the Website constitutes a solicitation, offer, opinion, or recommendation by Black Knight to buy or sell any security, or to provide legal, tax, accounting, or investment advice or services regarding the profitability or suitability of any security or investment.

**Your Consent to this Privacy Notice**

By submitting Personal Information and/or Browsing Information to Black Knight, you consent to the collection and use of information by us in compliance with this Privacy Notice unless you inform us otherwise by means of the procedure identified below. Amendments to the Privacy Notice will be posted on the Website. Your use of the Website following such publication of any amendment of this Privacy Notice will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms for all previously collected information and information collected from you in the future. We may use comments, information or feedback that you may submit in any manner that we may choose without notice or compensation to you.

If you have questions, would like to access your Personal Information, or want to opt-out of certain information sharing, please send your requests to:

Black Knight, Inc.  
601 Riverside Avenue  
Jacksonville, Florida 32204  
Attn: Chief Compliance Officer

904.854.5100  
(Toll-free) 833.256.4448

EFFECTIVE AS OF: SEPTEMBER 1, 2017  
LAST UPDATED: JANUARY 31, 2018

TM SM ® Trademark(s) of Black Knight IP Holding Company, LLC, or an affiliate.  
© 2014 – 2018. Black Knight, Inc. All rights reserved.
